<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>grxgs</title>
    <link>http://grxgs.com/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on grxgs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 16:30:01 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://grxgs.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;m learning and its timeline</title>
      <link>http://grxgs.com/blog/what-im-learning-and-timeline</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 16:30:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grxgs.com/blog/what-im-learning-and-timeline</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, it would be useful to layout exactly what I plan on learning. Having everything laid out and planned makes it easier to keep progressing. This timeline will be for 30 days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll primarily be focusing on learning (or relearning) the Python programming language. To accomplish this, I&amp;rsquo;ll be following &amp;ldquo;Python Crash Course&amp;rdquo; by Eric Matthes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I chose this particular book mainly for Part II of the book which is focused on 3 different types of projects. Along with that, each chapter ends with several exercises to reinforce the lessons. For anyone curious, I&amp;rsquo;ll be using Python 3 to go through the book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;timeline&#34;&gt;Timeline&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Days 1 - 5: Chapters 1 - 4&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Days 6 - 10: Chapters 5 - 8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Days 11 - 15: Chapters 9 - 11&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Days 16 - 20: Chapters 12 - 14 (Project 1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Days 21 - 25: Chapters 15 - 17 (Project 2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Days 26 - 30: Chapters 18 - 20 (Project 3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can find the table of contents for &amp;ldquo;Python Crash Course&amp;rdquo; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nostarch.com/pythoncrashcourse&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who remember learning programming this timeline is obviously aggressive. The reason this timeline is so aggressive is because I have previous programming experience. In Python at that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These 30 days will serve more as a reintroduction to the world of programming and Python. I&amp;rsquo;ll be posting updates every 5 days. However, you will see commits over on my &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grxgs&#34;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt; everyday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until next time&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash; grxgs&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://grxgs.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 09:32:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grxgs.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nothing here&amp;hellip;yet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://grxgs.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 09:32:23 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grxgs.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m going to try and keep this short and simple. I&amp;rsquo;m just a simple person whose trying to get into software development. Along with that, I&amp;rsquo;m also trying to improve my physical and mental health. If you want to know anything else, just reach out.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>http://grxgs.com/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 09:31:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grxgs.com/books/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Here you&amp;rsquo;ll find the books that I&amp;rsquo;m currently interested in reading. Currently, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty heavy towards business. Once I complete these, I&amp;rsquo;ll throw in some fiction for good measure. Recommendations are always welcome!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;currently-reading&#34;&gt;Currently Reading&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Sympathizer&lt;/strong&gt; - Viet Thanh Nguyen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;up-next&#34;&gt;Up Next&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Compound Effect&lt;/strong&gt; - Darren Hardy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Influence: Science and Principle&lt;/strong&gt; - Robert B. Cialdini&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Influence: The Psychology of Persuasion&lt;/strong&gt; - Robert B. Cialdini&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mindwise: Why We Misunderstand What Others Think, Believe, Feel, and Want&lt;/strong&gt; - Nicholas Epley&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sprint: How to Solve Big Problems and Test New Ideas in Just Five Days&lt;/strong&gt; - Jake Knapp and John Zeratsky&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Leadership Challenge: How to Make Extraordinary Things Happen in Organizations&lt;/strong&gt; - James M. Kouzes and Barry Z. Posner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post!</title>
      <link>http://grxgs.com/blog/first-post</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 22:31:41 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grxgs.com/blog/first-post</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kudos for stumbling upon this blog and more specifically this post. I&amp;rsquo;m not one for very long worded and fancy intros. So this will be a relatively short post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog has a few purposes. The main purpose is to have somewhere to record my hopefully mildly entertaining life experiences. You probably just asked yourself what type of life experiences might you expect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, this will focus on a two things really. First is my goal towards becoming employed as a software developer. I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved with technology in some capacity (more than less) for the past 7 years. After trying out a variety of roles, I figured I give software development an actual shot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondly is my fitness journey. As a desk jockey and former Pepsi enthusiast I am not in the &lt;em&gt;best&lt;/em&gt; shape I could be. After realizing that it&amp;rsquo;s easier to get in shape sooner than later figured I start now. As opposed to waiting until I&amp;rsquo;m in my 40s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the other purposes of this blog is hopefully serve as some motivation (for myself and others)as I progress. As time goes by, it would be great to look back at my former self and see how I&amp;rsquo;ve changed and improved. Along with that, it would be great if this blog convinced just one other person to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides that, there isn&amp;rsquo;t much more for me say. The next few posts you&amp;rsquo;ll see will talk about what I plan on learning and learning plan. Until next time&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;grxgs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>