<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on grxgs</title>
    <link>http://grxgs.com/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on grxgs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 22:31:41 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://grxgs.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post!</title>
      <link>http://grxgs.com/blog/first-post</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 22:31:41 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grxgs.com/blog/first-post</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kudos for stumbling upon this blog and more specifically this post. I&amp;rsquo;m not one for very long worded and fancy intros. So this will be a relatively short post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog has a few purposes. The main purpose is to have somewhere to record my hopefully mildly entertaining life experiences. You probably just asked yourself what type of life experiences might you expect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, this will focus on a two things really. First is my goal towards becoming employed as a software developer. I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved with technology in some capacity (more than less) for the past 7 years. After trying out a variety of roles, I figured I give software development an actual shot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondly is my fitness journey. As a desk jockey and former Pepsi enthusiast I am not in the &lt;em&gt;best&lt;/em&gt; shape I could be. After realizing that it&amp;rsquo;s easier to get in shape sooner than later figured I start now. As opposed to waiting until I&amp;rsquo;m in my 40s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the other purposes of this blog is hopefully serve as some motivation (for myself and others)as I progress. As time goes by, it would be great to look back at my former self and see how I&amp;rsquo;ve changed and improved. Along with that, it would be great if this blog convinced just one other person to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides that, there isn&amp;rsquo;t much more for me say. The next few posts you&amp;rsquo;ll see will talk about what I plan on learning and learning plan. Until next time&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;grxgs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>